

I am a highly experienced graphic designer with over 8 years of experience in the industry. I have worked on a wide variety of projects, from small scale local projects to large scale international ones. I have a very strong sense of aesthetics and an eye for detail, which makes me an excellent graphic designer. I am also very skilled in the use of various graphic design software programs, such as Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign, etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Graphic Designer - INDEGENE PRIVATE LIMITED

Aspen Block G4, 3rd Floor, Manyata Embassy Business Park, Outer Ring Road, Nagawara, Bengaluru - 560 045

Duties: Brochure, PPT Presentation, E-mailer Design, IDA, Logo

Client: Astrazeneca, Gilead, Illumya, Lynparza, Epclusa, Amgen, Aimovig, Aranesp, Avsola, Enbrel, Evenity, Kyprolis, Otezla, Prolia, Riabni.

Senior Graphic Designer - AL MANAR ADVERTISING

United arab emirates, Rolla, sharjah

Duties: Menu Card, Banners, Bill, Logo, Roll Up, Brochure,

Poster, Social Media

Graphic Designer - NSK CONSULTANTS

Kingdom of Saudi Arabia

Duties: Social Media, Brochure Designing, Poster, Roll Up

Graphic Designer - AD2PRO MEDIA SOLUTIONS

Chennai - India

Duties: Newspaper Advertisements, Magazine Advertisements, and Print Advertisements Design - **New Zealand Team**

SOFTWARE SKILLS



ADOBE PHOTOSHOP



ADOBE INDESIGN



ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR



ADOBE PREMIERE



ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS



POWERPOINT

ABDUL SHIYAS

GRAPHIC DESIGNER





+91 7907109903 🛇



2021-23

2019-21

2018-19

2015-18

shiyasgdr@gmail.com



Kerala, India

PORTFOLIO

CLICK/TOUCH TO OPEN

PASSPORT NO: X6757067

LICENSE: Valid UAE Driving License

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA

Graphic and Web Designing, Aptech Ltd, (Arena Animation)

HIGHER SECONDARY

Computer Commerce Majlis HSS, Valanchery, Puramannur

HIGH SCHOOL

MES HSS, Kerala state Board of Examination

LANGUAGES

English Malayalam Arabic Hindi

